Huh?
What's going on?
Hey!
That's dangerous!
A monkey?
Or a giant flying squirrel.
Hey!
No, it's just a cute girl.
Just what you were hoping for...
Hey!
Huh?
It's actually a person.
A child.
Be careful!
What are you doing?!
That's too high!
Come down!
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm looking for something!
But I can't seem to find it.
It's dangerous up there.
It feels great up here.
Why don't you come up here as well.
Huh?
C-Capisce!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look that way!
Now!
You won this time, Rina.
Th-That sound...
Glo!
It's a call from him!
H-Hello.
It's been a while, Madame Gloria.
I-It has been a while.
I've found the ideal princess candidate.
Huh? The ideal princess?
W-What do you mean?
The one who shall claim victory in the Grand Prix,
and ride atop the lead float in the Dream Parade...
...is PriPara's ideal princess.
I believe she should be arriving there shortly.
I'll be leaving her in your care.
Why did you come to Parajuku?
My prince asked me to.
Y-Your prince?
Yes, he's a truly wonderful person.
You know, I can't see forests or lakes here,
but I've always dreamed of living a city life.
I'm going to enjoy it to the fullest!
I-I see.
Yoohoo!
Fuwari, the girl from the Palps!
A princess candidate is coming here!
What should I do? What should I do?
Anyway, I should head out to greet her.
Good afternoon.
Yes, good aftern—
Hold it right there!
Yes?
What's with the goat?!
We became friends on the way here.
Take off your hat when you're inside!
Ah, pardon me.
But why do you have a goat?!
This is an introduction letter from him.
You're the ideal princess candidate?
Yes.
I'm Midorikaze Fuwari.
Nice to meet you.
You're...
PriPara's ideal princess who will ride
atop the lead float in the Dream Parade?!
She's... She's this girl that smells like goat mixed with grass, acorns, mushrooms, and deer droppings?!
I do remember him saying something about this...
I'm sure there must be a reason.
Understood.
This mountain smell that clings to you, I, Ookanda Gloria, and...
Rina!
...will cleanse you of it.
Here at Paprika Academy, you shall receive training that will take you from zero to being the ideal princess.
Stop!
Okay.
I'll do my best.
Spit it out!
Big news!
The PriPara princess scholarship
student is transferring in today!
Princess scholarship student?
It's the talk of the school!
I wonder what she's like.
I'm interested.
Her name's Midorikaze Fuwari.
She's from the Palps; a mountainous area in EuroPara.
Of course you'd know!
She's a second year in middle school,
but she's given special permission to live in the Paprika Academy High School dorms.
Really?!
Unprecedented!
Wait, we have a high school?
And dorms?
We do.
They've been around for quite some time.
They're behind the gymnasium.
Really? That's news to us!
How careless.
I couldn't read it.
But living in the dorms sounds fun.
I should mention: Ms. Ookanda is the headmistress.
On second thought, never mind.
Princess scholarship student, huh?
She'll be the center of attention in the
upcoming Summer Dream Idol Grand Prix.
Will she be a rival? Or a partner?
We don't know yet, but let us focus on PriPara.
Right!
Same goes for us!
Let's search for our next teammates!
...is what I'd like to say,
but I also have work I need to do
as the student council president.
I have to go meet the princess scholarship student now.
Really?!
Wow, we really do have a high school.
You don't have to come with me.
But I wanna meet her.
It would be rude if I didn't meet her fully dressed up.
Since she's the princess scholarship student,
I bet she'll look kinda like this.
She's so sparkly!
Midorikaze!
Why are you sleeping there?
Good morning, Ms. Gloria.
That bed is far too soft.
In the Palps, we'd always sleep on straw.
You mustn't!
You need to behave like a princess!
It's hard to move around in those pajamas.
Ah! It's you!
Oh, you're the girl from yesterday.
Huh? You know her?
Yeah, sort of.
It's nice to properly meet you.
I'm Manaka Laala.
I'm the Student Council President
and Head Disciplinarian, Minami Mirei.
I'm Houjou Sophy.
I'm a reincarnation of a jellyfish.
I'm Fuwari.
I'm aiming to be PriPara's ideal princess.
How much longer do you plan on being in your pajamas?
Hurry up and change into your school uniform.
I'll be fine in this instead.
This is easier to move in.
Ah! H-H-H-Hold it!
Ms. Gloria, may I take this off?
In the Palps, it was only the cows
and goats who wore collars.
That's a neck tie.
Please! It's suffocating!
My turn.
Huh?
Paprika Academy rule number 754:
"Students must address their teachers with respect"!
I'm sorry to do this right after you've changed schools,
but I'm issuing your first insubordination ticket!
Now that I get a better look at you,
you look just like one of my friends!
Huh? Friend?
Just like Komugi's tail and her cute behind!
Gah!
Rule number 43:
"Don't say that someone looks like a horse's butt"!
Waa!
All right, let's go.
Hey!
School's going to be fun!
Hey! Stop right there!
Fuwari seems like a really fun person.
Fuwari, get back here and accept your second ticket!
Yeah, a goat's friend is a friend of mine.
I can understand how she felt earlier,
but with my unrelenting guidance,
she'll surely become the ideal princess.
Right, Rina dear?
Let's see, Midorikaze will sit...
Ah, there's no one sitting next to Dorothy West.
So this is the princess candidate.
Oh well, if I get along with her,
maybe she'll join our five-person team.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah.
If you're a princess, then I'm a queen,
so you can call me "Your Highness".
She's got a tablet?!
She's got a lot of nerve for a middle schooler!
Is something wrong?
Wait. Is that a mini chalkboard?
It's because the goat will eat my paper...
Baa.
"Baa"?
That's my notebook!
She said it's delicious.
Man!
She's the super worst!
It's only been one day, but it's already been max craziness!
Don't eat my test too!
She said it's delicious.
What are you fishing in the pool for?
I caught it!
And when I wanted to eat my lunch...
What the heck are you doing?
Milking.
Happy birthday, baby birdy!
Don't go and hatch birds on my head!
It was infuriating!
In what universe is she princess-y?!
Calm down, Dorothy.
Relax. Relax.
Well, I can sympathize with Dorothy's feelings.
With one wrong step, freedom becomes selfishness.
Just like Go!
More like ego!
She thinks she can get away with anything
just because she might win!
Yes, yes.
With the way things are going, I wonder if
Fuwari will get used to school and PriPara...
You're worried, huh?
I was just talking about you, Fuwari!
Huh?
Oh, Laala!
What are you looking for this time?
PriPara.
I made a promise with my prince.
PriPara is a wonderful place overflowing with dreams, aspirations, and other beautiful things.
Will you become the ideal princess in PriPara for me?
Really?
Yes, I'd be glad to.
I wonder what kind of place PriPara is.
I can't wait to go!
Then let's go together.
Oh?
Hello, Ms. Meganee!
Ah, you have a new face with you.
Did you bring your PriTicket with you?
This, right?
My prince told me about it.
Then let's pick out your coord.
What's a coord?
She's searching for the brand that best fits you.
I wonder what kind of coord would look best on you.
The perfect brand for you is...
Th-There isn't one.
Huh?
What?
What?!
What do you mean there isn't a brand?
For some reason I can't find a coord that would fit her perfectly.
This is the first time something like this has happened.
No way...
I'll make a new brand that suits you on the double.
In the meantime, how about...
Please deal with these clothes for today.
I'm Laala.
What?!
Since her brand registration hasn't been completed,
she can't enter any shows.
Really? Isn't there anything you can do?
That's how the system works.
Man, I wanted to do a show in cute coords with Fuwari.
I'm sorry, Fuwari.
This is...
This is PriPara!
It's just like he described!
PriPara is a wonderful place.
I'm glad you think it's so great.
Oh, yeah!
There's more places I wanna show you over there.
Come on! Over here!
Wow!
There's so much greenery and flowers!
The air smells just like it does in Palps.
Kuma?!
Here I was drinking vegetable juice in a place like this,
and then you had to go and do that-kuma!
My precious vegetable juice...
I spilled 350ml of it-kuma!
I-I'm sorry.
Don't think you can just get off with an "I'm sorry"!
Hand over enough to fill a bathtub to show you're sorry-kuma!
You rooster...
Kuma?
Ku...
Kuma!
What a refreshing smile.
More like I've been healed by
a soft breeze across the plains-kuma.
I'm surprised to see a cute girl such as yourself here in PriPara-kuma.
It seems Kuma has also taken a liking to you, Fuwari.
Hm?
Is this a friend of yours, Laala?
Who is this girl-kuma?!
What's her name?
What year?
Blood type?
What's her type? Could it be a bear like me?
Type? A bear might be too much...
Fuwari?!
Where'd you go?!
Attention idols,
we'll be switching the hologrammation to artificial rain to water the flowers and greenery.
This was the system.
No way!
I'm getting all wet!
Let's wait in the café until it stops.
Huh?
What are you doing out there-pri?
I got separated from Fuwari.
Over there.
Huh?
What beautiful flowers.
And the rain feels great.
Fuwari?
Halt, my servant!
Wowzers! She's got such a big audience!
One must fear those who
hold the power to manipulate animals!
Mikan wants to be her friend!
This is the power of the princess candidate.
She has a charm that's different than any other girl-pri.
If we form a five person team with her,
I'm sure we'll be able to sweep the
Summer Dream Idol Grand Prix-pri!
Wow!
Hooray!
Yeah!
That was incredible, Fuwari!
Your voice is clearer than a jellyfish.
Even your impromptu show is great-pri.
Thanks!
But...
What do you mean "show"?
That's right. You've always lived in the mountains.
You've never seen a show before.
Would you show her?
Who? Me?
Easier said than done...
I'd love to see Laala's show.
Just get out there and show her-pri.
Well...
Capisce!
Please scan the appropriate number of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
An image of a sparkling hydrangea wet with rain.
The sheer frills are quite elegant!
Hydrangea Bouquet Coord!
Making Drama Switch On!
Princess...
Princess, where are you-kuma?!!
Kuma?
Flower garden in full bloom!
For you!
Lovely Flower Cinderella!
Kuma!
Cyalume Change!
That was wonderful, Laala.
This is PriPara.
This is a show.
I want to debut as soon as I can.
And become the ideal princess.
Laala, that was really, really wonderful.
Thanks.
All right, let's snap.
Okay.
How the heck did you snap cheese?!
It's authentic Palps cheese.
This is how you exchange Friend Tickets.
Let's do a concert together someday.
Yeah.
At this time, the rain will stop.
This was the system.
Oh, my prince...
I'll make sure to become a princess worthy of you.
Madame Gloria,
I'll be arriving shortly as well.
My prince,
I'll make sure to become a beautiful princess.
I look forward to it, my princess.
Why has Fuwari's prince come to Paprika Academy?
I want to sing at PriPara soon!
We'll help you search for a manager.
We'll make Fuwari our friend and be the next ones to do the Grand Prix.
If you say so, Dorothy.
Next time:
Prince and the Blue Bird of Sadness.
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!